我们可以使用一个接口来描述一个呼叫签名。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: We can use an interface
to describe a call signature.
我们只是用括号来描述一个函数。
And we're simply using parenthesis
here to this describe a function.
现在我们开始看到接口可以描述对象,
Now, what we're starting to see is
interfaces can describe objects,
接口可以描述函数。
interfaces can describe functions.
稍后，我们将看到接口可以描述数组。
In a moment, we'll see that
interfaces can describe arrays.
所以我们只处理 JavaScript 值
So we're dealing exclusively
with JavaScript values
从 JavaScript 对象类型扩展而来。
that extend from
the JavaScript object type.
我们还没有看到，我们也不会看到，一个界面能够
We've not yet seen, and we won't see,
an interface being able to
处理基元类型，或与类型(如字符串或数字)一起使用的运算符。
handle primitive types, or operators
used with types, like string or number.
没有办法用接口来描述它。
There is no way to describe
that with an interface.
这就是我们在这里看到的一个明显的区别。
So that's one clear
difference we're seeing here.
类型别名非常灵活。
Type aliases are extremely flexible.
他们可以处理原始的东西。
They can handle the primitive stuff.
它们可以处理接口可以处理的大多数事情。
They can handle most things
that an interface can handle.
接口可以处理的所有事情。
Everything that an interface can handle.
但是接口仅限于 JavaScript 对象和
But interfaces are limited
to JavaScript object and
子类型，包括数组和函数。
sub types which includes arrays and
functions.
有原型的东西，就这么想吧。
Things that have prototypes,
think of it that way.
这是一个函数签名。
So here is a function signature.
这里是类型的等价物，对吗？
And here is the equivalent with the type,
right?
包装在这里有点不合适，但是同样的想法。
The wrapping is a little unfortunate here,
but same idea.
这是一个签名，也是我想指出的唯一区别
This is one signature and
the only difference I wanna really point
因为它有点微妙，回报在这里是空白的，: 空白。
out cuz it's a little subtle,
the return is void here, :void.
为了使解析成为可能，我们在这里使用了胖箭头
And just to make parsing possible,
we use a fat arrow here
定义具有类型别名的函数类型时，这将无效。
to define a function type with a type
alias, this would not be valid.
关于函数类型有一个很酷的地方,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: One cool
thing about function types,
这里应该更漂亮一点。
a little prettier it's
supposed to be right here.
函数类型有一个很酷的地方，那就是我们可以得到一种叫做上下文推理的东西。
One cool thing about function types is we
get something called contextual inference.
我们已经定义了这种类型。
So we've already defined this type.
联系人1。
Contactmessenger1.
就在这里，对吧？
That's right up here, right?
迈克 · 诺斯: 看来我们不需要任何额外的工作了。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: It turns out like
we don't need any additional work.
没有额外的类型信息来确定返回类型应该是什么。
No additional type information in order to
figure out what the return type should be.
这些参数类型应该是什么。
What should these arguments type be.
或者论证时间应该是多少。
Or what should the argument times be.
这些都是免费的，因为这些信息都存在于这里。
That's all coming along for
free because that information exist here.
你会看到同样的好处通过回电，对不对？
You'll see the same benefit come
through with call backs, right?
如果你说我接受回电，它的价值就像签名应该是这样。
If you say I accept the call back and it's
value like the signature should be this.
现在，在每个调用站点上，每次你传回一个调用,
Now, at every invocation site,
every time you pass a call back along,
你可以忘记类型信息。
you can forget the type information.
类型检查仍然按照原来的方式进行，但是
The type checking still happens
exactly as it would, but
你不用一路上说得这么清楚。
you don't need to be so
explicit along the way.
Mike North: 构造签名看起来非常类似于调用签名。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Construct signatures
look very similar to call signatures.
你所需要的就是新的领导。
All you need is new head of that.
你已经习惯在课堂上看到这些了，对吧？
You're used to seeing this in a class,
right?
类是什么东西，它们是新的，我们可以使用新的关键字。
Classes are something, they're new-able,
we can use the new keyword with them.
所以这是一种描述实例化构造函数的方法
So this would be a way of describing
a constructor that instantiates either
有电子邮件地址或者电话号码的东西，而且肯定有名字。
things that have an email address or a
phone number, and definitely have a name.